Guide to the Records of the Tisch School of the Arts 1956-1981 (Bulk 1965-1981) RG 35
New York University Archives
- ACCESSION 93-025
  - Series V: Administrative Files
    - Sub-Committee/May, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - NYU Schools - Structure, undated (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - SOA Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Schechner Letter, undated (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - SOA/ Organizational Policy Committee, undated (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Nathan, G. Jean, undated (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Faculty Structure, NYU, undated (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Bobst library, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04225810 6
    - Byrnes, Joseph, Secretary, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Budget Office, 1968-1972 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Bureau of Public Occasions, 1971-1974 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Bursar Klebenoff, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Calendar Committee, Chairman David Oppenheim, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Chancellor's Office-Borowitz, Sidney, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Commission of Coordinated Liberal Studies, 1971-1974 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Commission on Student life, 1967-1969 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Commission Student Evaluation of Faculty, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Commission on Graduate and Professional Education, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - School of Continuing Education, Dean Smith, 1971-1973 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04225811 4
    - Second Annual Report, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Deans' Council, 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - M. de Capriles, V. P. and General Counsel, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Deafness Research and Training Center, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Executive Vice President (Brookner), 1970 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - School of Education, Dean Griffiths, 1970-1974 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - David Greene-Head All-University English, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Voting (NLRB) NYU, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Film Library, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Financial Aid- Brienza, Director, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Five Year Financial Plan, 1972-1977 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Thomas Bishop, Chairman French Dept. GSAS, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Inquires and Replies, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Lab Fee Structure- Interdepartmental Communication, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - League of Professional Theatre, Training Programs, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Interdepartmental Communication - regarding Library, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Interdepartmental Communication - correspondence Lee Mank, Assistant Dean, 1969, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Martin Luther King Awards, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Memos to SOA Faculty, students, staff-, 1969, 1971-1972, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04225812 2
    - Memos to SOA Department Chairmen, 1971, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Memos to SOA faculty, 1970, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Memos to SOA students, 1970-1972 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Miller, J. Michael; Associate Dean -Interdepartmental Communication, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Ombudsman, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Orientation, 1969-1971 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Perception Course, Peter Phillips, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Publicity, 1971-1972, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Ramsay Louise, Assistant Dean -Interdepartmental Communication, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Recorder - Tatum, N, 1969, 1971, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Rockefeller Grant, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Schedules, Assignments etc., 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Space Rental, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Speeches & Notes, David Oppenheim, 1969-1970, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Staff meetings, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Student Evaluation of Faculty, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Student Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Student Film Ownership, 1969-1972, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Student Films -Oxford Films Contracts, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04225813 0
    - Student Government, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Student Lists, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Student Recommendations, 1972, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Student Senatorial Election - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - The Drama Review, 1972-1974 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Video Access Center, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Walt Disney College Film -Writing contest, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Year- End Reports, 1969-1970, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Zuelke, F -misc., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Sawhill: Weekly meetings with deans: Dec., 1979 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Meetings: SOA Faculty, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Meeting: SOA Faculty 3/7/77, undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Meetings: SOA Faculty, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Meeting: SOA Faculty 4/21/76, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04225814 8
    - Meeting: SOA Faculty 3/1/76, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Meeting: SOA Faculty 12/16/76, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Meeting: SOA faculty 10/27/76, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Meetings: SOA Dept. Chairmen Fall 1975-Winter 1979 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Michelson, Annette: Recommendation for tenure, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Miller, J. Michael (Assoc. Dean, SOA) Memos, 1976, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Miller, J. Michael Memos, 1969-75, 1969-1975 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Miller, J. Michael Memos, Fall 1975-Spring 1976 1975- (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Minichiello, Michael (Sec. to Dean Oppenheim) Memos, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Minneapolis-St.Paul Oppenheim trip, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Museum of the City of New York, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1974-1978 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1974-1978 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - News Bureau, NYU, 1974-1977 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04225815 5
    - News Bureau Press Releases, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - News Bureau, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - News Bureau, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Oliva, L. Jay, Vice Chancellor for Planning, 1976-1978 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - S, 1970-1978 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - S, 1970-1978 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Sawhill, 1977-1979 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Sawhill, 1977-1979 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Sawhill, weekly meetings with Deans, Sept.-Dec. 1978 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Sawhill, weekly meetings with Deans, Sept.-Dec. 1978 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Sawhill, thank you letters to donors, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Acting Courses for Law Students, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04225816 3
    - Admissions, H Livesey, director of, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Advertising, Barton-Gillet Co, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Advertising, Frank Lopez, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Advertising, Jameson School, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Advertising, Student Film Festivals, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Advertising, Summer Session, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Advertising Tallies, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Alternate Media Center, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Alternate Media Center, Catalogue, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Alternate Media Center, Memos DO/Red Burns; Burns/anyone, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Alternate Media Center: NSF Project, Reading Consortium, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Alumni Federation, Dinner for President Sawhill, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - The American Cinematheque, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - American Film Institute, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - American Film Institute Legislation, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Awards, SOA Students, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Borowitz, Dr Sidney, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Budget Policy Advisory Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Buildings, SOA, Paul Stone, Mgr, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Ciestale, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - City Center of Music and Drama, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Clippings, NB: Not SOA or NYU publicity, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Commencement, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Course Information Sheets-SOA Departments, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Deans' Council, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Dept of Acting, memos DO/Shapli; Shapli/anyone, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Dept of Acting and Drama: Conflicts, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Dept of Acting, NEA Grant, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Dept of Cinema Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Dept of Dance, memos DO/Stuart Hodes; Hodes/anyone, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Dept of Design, memos DO/Burlingame; Burlingame/anyone, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Dept of Design, Annual Design Show, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Dept of Directing, memos DO/Carl Weber; Weber/anyone, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Dept of Drama, UG, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Dept of Drama, memos DO/Flakes; Flakes/anyone, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Dept of Drama, UG, Sue Flakes Audition Tour, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Dept of Drama, Grad Memos DO/Kirby; Kirby/anyone, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - GFTV, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - GFTV, memos DO/Mel Howard; Howard/anyone, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - UGFTV, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - UGFTV, memos DO/Haig Manoogian; Manoogian/anyone, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Eugene, Joseph, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04225817 1
    - Faculty Organization Committee, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Voting Rights Committee, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Film Awards, Students and Alumni, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Film, misc info, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Film Festival, Carnegie Hall Cinema, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Film Festival, Carnegie Hall, Fairchild Party, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Film Festival, Carnegie Hall, Reception, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Film Festival, Loeb, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Film Festival Loeb, 30th, 31st, 32nd, 33rd Annual, 1971-1973 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Film Society of Lincoln Center, undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Financial Aid, undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Flakes, Sue, Chairman UG Drama, Personal File, undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Goals Statement 11/13/75, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Goals Study, undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Godfather II, Student Film, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Graduate Commission, undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Hester, Dr James M (NYU president), undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Howard, Mel (Head of GFTV) Personal File, undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Incoming FYI and routing, Jul 1975 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Incoming FYI and routing, Jun 1975 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Incoming FYI and routing, May 1975 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Incoming FYI and routing, Apr 1975 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Incoming FYI and routing, Mar 1975 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Incoming FYI and routing, Feb 1975 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Incoming FYI and routing, Jan 1975 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Incoming FYI and routing, Dec 1974 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Incoming FYI and routing, Nov 1974 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Incoming FYI and routing, Oct 1974 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Incoming FYI and routing, Sep 1974 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Incoming FYI and routing, Fall 1974-Summer 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Incoming Memoranda, NYU Deans, Administrators and offices, Fall 1974-Summer 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Incoming Memoranda, NYU Deans, Administrators and Offices, Fall, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Incoming Memos NYU Deans etc Fall, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Incoming Memos NYU Deans etc Responses by DO, Fall 1975 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Incoming Memos NYU Deans etc Responses by DO, Fall 1974-Summer 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Kirby, James C Memos, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04226075 5
    - L, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - League of Professional Theater Training Programs, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Levy, Richard M Faculty Theater Program, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Levine, Jonathan, Student, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Lomax, Daniel P Faculty Design, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Meetings, Dept Chairmen, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Meetings, SOA Faculty Dec 10, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Meetings, SOA Faculty Nov 11, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Meetings, SOA Faculty May 15, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Meetings, SOA Faculty March 20, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Myers, Morton; Director of University Budget, undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Miller, Michael J Memoranda, undated (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Mininberg, Dr Elliott, Assistant Deputy Chancellor, undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Undesignated Filing, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Undesignated Filing, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - News Bureau, Press Releases, undated (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Park, Jacqueline, Assoc Professor, UGFTV, undated (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Perception (course), undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Public Occasions, NYU Bureau of, undated (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Publicity SOA, undated (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Publicity SOA, undated (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Ramsay, Louise A Assistant Dean; Memoranda Summer, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Ramsay, Louise A Assistant Dean; Spring 1975 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Ramsay, Louise A Fall, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Ramsay, Louise A Summer, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Regents Regional Coordinating Council for Post Secondary Education in NYC; comm't on Performing Arts, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04226076 3
    - Regents Council; previous and current meetings, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Regents Council; subcommittee notes, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller Study Group, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Royal Shakespeare Residency; report to DO Aug 1, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Royal Shakespeare Residency; SOA report, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - NEH Work File, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Royal Shakespeare-Student Diaries, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Royal Shakespeare-misc correspondence, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Royal Shakespeare-Student Diaries, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Royal Shakespeare-NEH Grant Applications, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Royal Shakespeare-NEH, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Royal Shakespeare-Report, undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Royal Shakespeare-NEH Report, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Royal Shakespeare-Norman Floyd Report, undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Royal Shakespeare-Gister Report, undated (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Royal Shakespeare-NEH Proposal, undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Senate; NYU, undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Senate Educational Policies Comm't, undated (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Shaliko Co, undated (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Silver Towers Rental Office, undated (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Slater, Reggie; Student Files Access Law, undated (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Student Records and Registration; Office of, undated (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Summer Session, SOA, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Summer Session, Memos from DO/Falk; Falk/Anyone, undated (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Summer Session, Bennett College Pre-College Dance Program, undated (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Summer Session, NYU, undated (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - TV, miscellaneous, undated (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Former Faculty A-Z, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04226077 1
    - Prospective Faculty A-J, 1969-1971 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Prospective Faculty K-Z, 1969-1971 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Designations, 1968-1970 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Faculty, 1970-1972 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Study by Arts Development Associates, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Students Choosing School of the Arts and NYU School of the Arts Seeking Students, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Prospective Faculty (including guest speakers), A-I, 1971-1974 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Prospective Faculty (including guest speakers), J-R, 1971-1974 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Prospective Faculty (including guest speakers), S-Z, 1971-1974 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Applicants, assistant dean position, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Current Faculty, A-Z, 1969-1974 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - School of the Arts Council, 1968-1973 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04226078 9
    - Vice Chancellor for Academic Affairs, Bromberg, 1969-1974 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Vice Chancellor for Academic Affairs, Bromberg, Berezin, 1969-1974 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Admissions, Director-Livesey, 1968-1971 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Goren, Vice Chancellor, Admissions Aid, 1969-1974 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - NYU Admissions Committee (Oppenheim's papers), 1969-1973 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Affirmative Action program, 1972-1974 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Affirmative Action program, 1968-1971 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Alumni Federation of NYU, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Alumni Club, 1972-1974 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Art Collection, 1969-1972 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Assistant Chancellor for Administration, Samuel T. Burneson, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Assistant Chancellor for Administration, Hugh C. Banks, 1968-1971 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Academy of TV Arts and Sciences Agreement, 1965-1974 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04226079 7
    - Advertising, Barton-Gillet, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Advertising, Jameson, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Advertising Campaign, 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Alternative Media Center, 1970-1972 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Alternative Media Center, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Alumni, 1970-1973 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Annual Report, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Budget, 1968-1972 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Budget, Joseph Eugene, 1972-1974 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Budgets, Departmental, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Budget Estimates, 1973-1975 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Budget Officer, Floyd Taylor, 1969-1972 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Buildings Manager, operations, Paul Stone, 1966-1974 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Course Information Sheets, 1969-1971 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Department of Acting, 1969-1974 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Recruitment Acting Dept., 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Perry, Ted, Chairman, Dept. of Cinema Studies, 1972-1974 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Department of Dance, 1971-1974 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Dance Collective, 1971-1974 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04226080 5
    - Department of Directing, Shapiro, 1970-1974 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Film Comment, Cinema Studies, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Department of Design, 1971-1974 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Department of Drama, 1972-1974 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Department of Graduate Drama, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Department of Undergraduate Film and T.V. (UGFTV), 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Department of Undergraduate Film and T.V. (UGFTV), 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Department of Graduate Film, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Committee of Combining Film Resources, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Department of Film, Leo Hurwitz, 1970-1972 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Film and T.V., Equipment (incl C. Milne, memos), 1969-1974 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Film Festivals, 1971-1974 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Reorganization of Graduate Program of the Institute of Film and Television, 1971-1973 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Theatre Dept., Registration Schedule, Fall 1974 + misc., 1971-1974 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Theatre Department, Central Notion Company, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Theatre Program, Nov. 1971 -Aug. 1972, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Theatre Program, Sept. 1972 -Aug. 1973, 1972-1973 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Theatre Program, Sept. 1973 -Dec. 1974, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Theatre Program, Ensemble Theatre Project, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Theatre Program, Manhattan Project, A. Gregory, director, 1968-1973 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Theatre Program, Productions, K. De Francis, Co-ordinator, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Theatre Program, St. Croix Project, Carl Weber, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Theatre Program, Section 10, undated (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Theatre Program, Shaliko Company, undated (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Development, 1967-1972 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04226081 3
    - Faculty Grievance Committee, 1971-1974 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1968-1973 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Promotions, 1971-1973 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Tenure Committee, 1970-1973 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Voting, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Financial Aid Scholarships (incl. Disney Foundation), 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Grading, 1969-1971 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Graduate Assistants, 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Graduating Students, 1969-1973 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Office Services, Josephine Schrimpe, Director, 1970-1972 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Oliva, L. Jay, V.P. Academic Planning, "Project on Change in Undergraduate Liberal Education", 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Personnel Department, William Jones, Director, 1969-1974 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - President's Office, Hester, Feb., 1969-1972 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - President's Office, Hester, Sept., 1972-Jun 1974 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - President Hester, Cocktail Parties, Feb., Feb 1972-Mar 1974 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Public Relations, 1970-1974 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Purchasing Department, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Real Estate, Ray Viola, Director, 1969-1974 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Real Estate Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Roberto, Joseph, University Architect, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Registrar, 1969-1973 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Sponsored Research Office, Sidney Roth, Director, 1969-1971 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Sponsored Research Office, Sidney Roth, Director, 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Sponsored Research Office, Sidney Roth, Director, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Sponsored Research Office, Sidney Roth, Director, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Status of Alumni Giving, 1972-1974 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Student Affairs, Jane Maggin, Director, Jun 1968-Aug 1971 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Student Affairs, Jane Maggin, Director, Sep 1971-Jun 1974 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Student Records Report Sub-Committee, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Task Force and Financial Emergency, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      bar code#: 3 1142 04226082 1
    - Tenure Comm't - D. Oppenheim, Chair Sub-Comm't on Alternatives to Tenure, 1971-1972 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Tenure Comm't - D. Oppenheim, Chair Sub-Comm't on Alternatives to Tenure, 1972-1974 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Tenure - General Corresp. - D. Oppenheim, Member Ad Hoc Comm't to Study Tenure, 1967-1972 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Tenure - General Corresp. - D. Oppenheim, Member Ad Hoc Comm't to Study Tenure, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Town Hall, Jerrold Ross (music education), 1972 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Treasurer's Office, Joseph Whiteside, 1970-1971 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - University College (incl. Dean Borowitz and Alumni Survey), 1971 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - University Without Walls, Herb London, Director, 1971-1974 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Washington Sq. Council Meetings - memos to D. Oppenheim, 1970-1973 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Washington Square College, Dean Bayly Winder, 1968-1974 (Box 31, Folder 11)